我們繼續朝東走?
So, we keep headin' east?
是的 就這麼想的
Yeah, that's the idea.
遠離大城市?
Stay out of the big cities?
是啊
Uh-huh.
我覺得我都厭倦了
I think I'm tired.
是啊 我也是
Yeah. Me, too.
拿著
Here.
把車開到辦公室門口
Bring it on up to the office.
我去結帳
I'm going to go check us out.
好的
All right.
" 我匆匆趕路 "
" With the rushin' that way "
" 有一種感覺  那就是我的生活 "
" I had a feeling it was my day "
" 這麼多個日夜 "
" For one of those nights "
" 當你青春不在時  你會感到遺憾 "
" When you lose your cool, and you're feelin' sorry "
" 你所犯的錯就像故事書中所寫 "
" You're ridin' on sin to the page of a story "
" 又是蠢人的一天 "
" Of another great night in the life of a fool "
你幹什麼那麼久?
What took you so long?
沒什麼
Nothing.
我和服務員有點不愉快
I had a little trouble with the maid...
現在好了
but everything's fine now.
媽的
Damn.
才8:00
8:00.
就已經這麼熱了
It's already this hot.
我們還有水嗎?
How are we fixed for water?
可能快不夠了
Probably not enough.
確實是
Yeah.
在辦公室後面有一個製冷的飲水機
There's a cooler in the back in the office.
嘿
Hey.
啊  啊  啊
Aah! Aah! Aah!
莎拉 親愛的 怎麼了?
Sarah, honey, what's wrong?
怎麼了 寶貝?
What is it, sweetie? Hmm?
- 爸爸  - 恩?
- Daddy. - Yeah?
- 爸爸  - 爸爸在這裡
- Daddy. - Daddy's here.
- 爸爸在這裡  - 我夢到了妖怪
- Daddy's here. - There were monsters.
不  寶貝 世界上沒有妖怪
No, sweetie. There's no such thing as monsters.
你只是做了一個噩夢
You were just having a bad dream.
怎麼了 爸爸?
What's wrong, Dad?
嗨 老兄  莎拉做了個噩夢而已
Hi, kiddo. Sarah's just having a bad dream.
我看到妖怪  傑克
I saw monsters, Jack.
妖怪?
Monsters?
什麼樣子的?
What kind?
我不知道  它們從我的衣櫃裡鑽了出來
I don't know. They came out of my closet...
然後  他們一直在黑影裡
and then they were in the shadows.
噢  黑影妖怪
Mmm, shadow monsters.
好吧 它們看起來是有點可怕
Well, they look pretty scary...
但是他們什麼事情也不能做
but they really can't do anything...
尤其是當光照在它們身上的時候
especially when the lights are on.
他們怕光
They're scared of the light.
怎麼了 寶貝?
What happened, baby?
- 你還好吧?  - 我很好
- You OK? - I'm OK.
莎拉剛才做夢 夢到了妖怪
Sarah had a bad dream about monsters.
- 噢  - 我正在給她說
- Oh. - And I was telling her...
實際上沒有妖怪這種東西
that there's no such thing as monsters.
我打開手電筒以防萬一
I'm going to turn on my night light just in case.
聽起來是個不錯的主意
That sounds like a brilliant solution.
- 嘿 傑克?  - 嘿 媽媽?
- Hey, Jack? - Hey, Mom?
早上好
Morning.
早上好  寶貝
Morning, baby.
嘿  親愛的  今天早上沒有車來接我
Hey, hon, the pick up still won't start.
你不介意順路把我帶過去?
You mind dropping me off on the way in?
好的
Sure.
- 你喂了巴羅了嗎?  - 是的  已經喂了
- Did you feed Burrow? - Yeah, I fed him.
好的  很好
All right. Good.
手電筒有作用嗎?
The night light worked, didn't it?
我自己來  爸爸
I got it, Dad.
今天你準備幹什麼  傑克?
What do you got going today, Jack?
沒什麼  還有幾天就數學考試了
Uh, nothing much. A math test in a few days...
今天體育課的時候要打棒球
and I think we're playing baseball in gym class today...
我希望我今天能打的更好
so I can look forward to sucking hard in right field.
好的  只要記住
Well, just remember...
別讓擊球手把球打飛過你的頭
don't let the hitter get the ball over your head...
除非是打出了場地
Unless it's out of the park.
是啊
Well, yeah.
我今天可以早點下班  我今天的工作只是
I get off early today. All I have...
沃森威爾得拖拉機銷售宴
is the Watsons-Willard Day bride's tractor sale.
你想要我來接你嗎?
You want me to pick you up?
是的
Yeah.
我們可以坐在汽車裡看電影  然後解決一些事情
Then we can go to the drive-in and make out tonight.
自從70年代就
There hasn't been a drive-in here...
這裡沒有免下車影院了  但是
since the early seventies, but...
我愛你
I love you.
- 過的愉快  - 你也是
- Have a good one. - You, too.
- 早上好  - 德里克
- Morning. - Derek.
- 嗨  湯姆  - 早上好  約瑟夫
- Hey, Tom. - Morning, Joseph.
真是瘋狂
That's wild.
- 嗨  湯姆  - 早上好  派特
- Hey, Tom. - Morning, Pat.
- 嘿 麥克  - 湯姆
- Hey, Mick. - Tom.
查利今天早上要稍微晚些到
Charles is going to be a little late this morning.
- 他又喝醉了?  - 是啊 我猜也是.
- Is he drunk again? - Yeah, I guess.
嘿  你約會過最瘋狂的女人是誰?
Hey, who's the craziest woman you ever dated?
我?
Me?
是啊  麥克和我正在談論
Yeah. Mick and me, we were talking...
原來和我們在一起過的女人
about some of the girls we went with.
- 噢.  - 有次他和一個女人約會
- Uh-huh. - He once dated a girl...
那個女的在半夜企圖襲擊他
who used to attack him in the middle of the night.
- 她怎麼了?  - 是啊
- She what? - Yeah.
她經常做一些莫名其妙的夢
She used to have these crazy goddamn dreams...
夢見她的男朋友
where instead of her boyfriend...
變成了精神錯亂的殺人狂
I was some kind of demented killer.
有天半夜我醒來  她居然把一把叉子插在我的肩膀上
I woke up one night, she stuck a goddamn fork in my shoulder.
- 你在開玩笑吧  - 沒有  我血濺當場
- You're kidding me. - No. I'm spurting blood.
她就坐在那裡
She's sitting there crying...
哭說著  "親愛的 我愛你 我愛你"
going, "Baby, I love you, I love you."
然後怎麼了?  你和他分手了 對吧?
So, what happened? You broke up with her, right?
沒有  我和她結了婚.
No, I married her.
嘿  還在一起6年
Hey, it lasted six years.
人非聖賢  湯姆
Nobody's perfect, Tom.
我不這樣認為
I guess not.
把這傢伙打出局  我們準備好  開始
Strike this guy out. We got 'em. Let's go.
- 耶  - 耶
- Yeah. - Yeah.
2次 出局.
Two out.
這局贏了  歡呼吧  兄弟們
One winning run coming right up, boys.
- 加油  博比  - 呼
- Go, Bobby! - Whoo!
沒關係  比利
It's all right, Billy.
注意  注意
Look alive, look alive.
耶
Yeah!
得球
Ball.
耶  居然這樣
Yeah, that's it.
他什麼都沒打到  他什麼都沒打到
He's got nothing. He's got nothing.
準備  準備  再來一次  加油
Let's go, let's go. One more. Come on, now.
加油  博比
Come on, Bobby.
耶 你吃定他了
Yeah. He's yours, he's yours.
- 噢  - 呼
- Oh! - Whoo!
- 呼  - 對你來說簡單  傑克  加油 傑克
- Whoo! - Easy, Jack. Come on, Jack.
別放棄  傑克
Don't drop it, Jack!
- 你接的住 傑克  - 傑克 你這個倒楣蛋
- That's yours. Come on. - Jinx, Jackie boy!
- 噢  - 噢
- Oh! - Oh!
比賽結束  黃隊贏了 走吧
Game over! Yellows win. Let's go, guys.
泰勒  戴爾切克  你們拿好器材 走吧
Taylor, Dietrich, you're on equipment. Let's go.
兄弟們 來 走吧
Guys, come on. Let's go.
- 打的不錯 博比.  - 你被打敗了 博比
- Good try, Bobby. - You was robbed, Bobby.
大家都去沖個涼
Everyone hit the showers.
- 太棒了  - 不錯
- Awesome. - Nice.
打的好
Good job.
如你所願  你出名了 是嗎 史多?
Guess you think you're hot shit, huh, Stall?
什麼?  沒 我沒有啊
What? No, I don't.
我們的小英雄 對吧?
Little hero here, huh?
這裡的小明星
Little superstar here.
小英雄在最後一分鐘拯救了世界 對吧?
Little hero saves the day at the last minute, right?
博比 這只是個比賽而已
Bobby, it's just a game, OK?
只是一場愚蠢的體育課
It's just stupid gym class.
你說誰蠢?
Who you calling stupid?
呃  我是說體育課很蠢
Ahem. No, I said gym class was stupid.
"我是說體育課很...."  大家聽聽這個小同性戀說的
"No, I said gym class was..." Listen to this little faggot.
是啊 你說對了
Yeah. You're right.
我既渺小又是同性戀
I'm both little and a faggot.
你來找我麻煩是為了伸張正義?
You got me dead to rights.
來啊 娘娘腔  這個這麼樣?
Come on, chickenshit, let's do this.
你到底要怎麼樣?
What would be the point?
我的意思是 算你贏了  你贏了 你贏了
I mean, you win. You win, you win.
你得到了你想要的地位
You've established your alpha male standing.
你讓我變的渺小
You've established my unworthiness.
不過這樣兇狠的對我 是不是有點..
But doing violence to me just seems... ahem...
有點殘忍和沒意思  你不覺得嗎?
pointless and cruel, don't you think?
你這個廢物臭婊子
Let's do this, you punk bitch.
是不是該說渺小的婊子同性戀廢物?
Shouldn't that be little punk ass chickenshit faggot bitch?
婊子同性戀廢物
Chickenshit faggot bitch.
噢
Uh-oh.
天啊
God!
博比才是真的渺小
Bobby is a chickenshit.
嘿  帥哥
Hey, good looking.
我們現在去哪裡?
Where are we going?
傑克在裘蒂·丹佛斯家學習
Well, Jack's studying over at Judy Danvers'...
莎拉有馬薩在照顧
and Martha's taking care of Sarah.
- 是嗎?  - 是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
那我們去哪裡?
So, where are we going?
我們好久沒有年輕的感覺了
We never got to be teenagers together.
是嗎?
Uh-huh.
待會兒你就知道了
I'm going to fix that.
你在裡面幹什麼?
What's going on in there?
別脫你的衣服 我馬上就好
Keep your shirt on. I'm coming.
我的天啊
Holy cow.
什麼?
What?
你需要有人來幫你嗎?  帥哥
Do you need some help with that, big boy?
呃  也許吧
Uh... maybe.
噢 我的上帝啊
Oh, my God.
你對我的妻子都做了些什麼?
What have you done with my wife?
好了嗎?  開始!
Ready? OK!
出發吧  野貓!
Go, Wildcats!
先生  這裡沒有妻子
No wives in here, mister.
- 嗷  - 唏
- Wow. - Shh.
小聲點  我爸媽都在隔壁
Quiet. My parents are in the next room.
你這個淘氣鬼
You're naughty.
你在幹什麼?
What are you doing?
沒什麼
Nothing.
你真是個壞孩子
You are such a bad boy.
好啊 好啊 姐妹們 好啊 ?
Rah, rah, sis, boom, bah.
這種東西在中學裡可不多見
There wasn't much of that in high school.
啊
Ah...
怎麼了?
What is it?
我還記得我們原來相愛的時候
I remember the moment I knew you were in love with me.
我從你眼睛裡看到的
I saw it in your eyes.
我到現在都可以看到
I can still see it.
你當然可以
Of course you can.
我一直愛著你
I still love you.
我是世上最幸運的混蛋
I'm the luckiest son of a bitch alive.
你是我所認識的最好的男人
You are the best man I've ever known.
和幸運沒有任何關係
There's no luck involved.
[路人]你想下車去弄點吃的和其他的東西嗎?
You want to go down and get some food or something?
你想像過一百年前的孩子
You ever wonder what kids did for fun...
在週末的晚上玩什麼嗎?
on a Saturday night a hundred years ago?
我不知道
I don't know.
我原來經常想像
I guess I always figured...
他們偷偷駕著父母的馬車
they got into their parents' wagon...
在毒販和娼妓活動的街上來來回回
and went cruising up and down their main drag...
像白癡一樣的使勁的彈著班卓琴
playing loud banjo music and acting like idiots.
這個就是你所想像的?
So, you think this is as good as it gets?
你是說我們嗎?  是的
For us? Yeah.
現在就差不多
For now.
實際上  我們長大了 有了工作 談戀愛
Eventually, we... we grow up, we get jobs, we have affairs...
還成了經常酗酒的酒鬼
and we become alcoholics.
呃  你要知道 有時候
Ahem. You know, sometimes...
你總是讓我更沮喪
you depress me.
嘿  我就擅長這個
Hey, that's what I'm good at.
給我
Give me that.
嘿  那邊不是那個姓史多的同性戀嗎?
Hey, isn't that that Stall faggot?
是的
Yeah.
你該去打他一頓
You should go kick his ass.
我會的
I'm going to.
他媽的 他是誰?
Who the fuck was that?
我不知道  我也不想知道
I don't know, and I don't want to know.
這個偏僻的小城讓我感到噁心
Can I just say how sick I am of these podunk towns...
誰會住在這個偏僻的小城裡?
and the goddamn podunks who live in 'em?
你知道嗎  如果你繼續這樣說的話
Do you think if you keep saying that...
這裡將會有一些變化
it's actually going to change anything?
這裡就是讓我感到噁心
I am so sick of this shit.
你在10`000英里前就這樣說了
Yeah, you made that clear about ten thousand miles ago.
如果現在你沒有更好的建議
Now, if you haven't got a better idea...
我不想再聽你說這個了
I don't want to hear about it anymore.
我們現在真他媽的窮
We are so goddamned broke.
是啊  那麼
Yeah, well...
這很容易辦
that's easy to fix.
沒門
No way.
- 來吧  - 不
- Come on. - Mm-mmm.
你今天晚上和吉米一起嗎?
Are you going to go shoot pool with Jerry?
可能吧
Maybe.
謝謝 湯姆  謝謝 麥克 你們一直那麼棒
Thanks, Tom. Thanks, Mick... good as ever.
再見
There you go.
教堂見
See you in church.
好的 願你們晚上過的好
Yep. Have a good evening.
你也一樣  回見 夏洛特
You, too. See you tonight, Charlotte.
好的 回見
Yeah. See you.
噢  對不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
噢  沒關係 老傢伙
Aw, it's all right, old fella.
朋友 我們打烊了
Just closing up, fellas.
黑咖啡
Coffee, black.
我也一樣  我還要些派  要檸檬味的
The same. I'll have some pie... some of that lemon meringue pie.
朋友們  不好意思  我們打烊了
Guys, guys, I'm sorry. I'm... We're closed.
我說了  咖啡
I said... coffee!
好吧
OK.
我覺得我們能做好的
I guess we can handle that.
咖啡不是很新鮮
It's not very fresh.
你可以回去了 夏洛特
You can go home now, Charlotte.
我來拿派就是了
Just leave the pie.
比利
Billy...
親愛的 你要在這裡留一會兒
You're going to be sticking around for a while, honey.
湯姆?
Tom?
他媽的別動
Don't fuckin' move.
先生 我們沒有  我們沒有太多的現金
Sir, we don't... we don't carry much cash here.
你們做什麼都可以
You gentlemen are certainly welcome to all of it.
混蛋 這我知道  相信我
Oh, I know that, asshole, believe me.
我很清楚
I do know that.
- 啊  - 閉嘴 婊子
- Aah! - Shut up, bitch!
好了 比利
OK, Billy...
讓這個混蛋瞧瞧我們不是說著玩的
let's show this asshole we mean business.
什麼?  她?
What? Her?
是的  她
Yes, her.
殺了她
Do her!
- 啊
- Aah! - Uhh.
我告訴你  那些人
I'm telling you, those men were...
他們要殺掉我們
They were going to kill us.
如果沒有湯姆的話  他們就殺掉我們了
They were going to kill us, and if it weren't for Tom...
他真是一個英雄
He's a hero.
....和國內幾宗謀殺案有關係
...in conjunction with several murders in those states.
湯姆·史多  一個居家男人
Now, Tom Stall is a family man...
長期工作在社區
with longstanding ties to this community.
湯姆·史多  是一個努力工作的
Tom Stall was just another hard-working...
做小生意的商人
small business owner and operator...
在印地安那州的密佈努克  而現在
in Millbrook, Indiana, but now...
呃  其中有一個拿著槍指著我的頭
Um, one of the guys had a... a gun to my head...
然後湯姆  他真是神了 他
and Tom... He was amazing. He...
嗨  親愛的
Hi, baby.
- 嘿 親愛的  - 你怎麼樣了?
- Hey, honey. - How you doing?
你還好嗎?
How are you?
你聽到這些關於我的事情不覺得噁心嗎?
Are you as sick of hearing about me as I am?
不啊 我還挺喜歡
No, I kind of like it.
看  你的照片都在報紙上了
Look. Your picture's in the paper.
我的天啊
Oh, God.
小心點
Careful.
- 嗨 孩子們  - 媽媽
- Hi, guys. - Mom.
我現在能站起來嗎?
Can l... Can I get up now?
- 你能行的  爸爸  - 是的
- You got it, Dad? - Yeah.
- 幹的好 湯姆  - 我們都支持你 湯姆
- Way to go, Tommy. - We're all here for you, Tom.
幹的好 湯姆
Way to go, Tom.
- 嗨 寶貝  - 噢 這太好了
- Hi, sweetie. - Oh, that's so nice.
非常感謝大家來到這裡
Thank you so much for coming.
我們現在正在密爾布努克州
We're in Millbrook, just outside the home...
在美國英雄 湯姆·史多 的家門口
of American hero Tom Stall...
他剛和他的家人從醫院回來
who's just now returning from the hospital with his family.
史多先生  我是WRPK新聞電視臺的珍尼·懷亞特
Mr. Stall, Jenny Wyatt, WRPK news.
我想採訪你幾個問題
I have a few questions for you. How did it feel...
當你面隊那些無情的殺人狂
when you saw the guns of those ruthless killers...
拿著槍直指你頭的時候  你有什麼感覺?
pointed directly at you?
- 有什麼感覺嗎?  - 對
- How did it feel? - Yeah.
感覺不怎麼好
Not very good.
你自己也不驚訝嗎?
Were you surprised, though...
在那種情況下你有如此的反映
by your own reaction to the situation?
呃  我所做的
Uh... what I did was...
我的意思是說  任何人都會這樣做
I mean, anybody would have done that.
那只是一件  一件可怕的事情
It was just... It was a terrible thing.
我覺得這事情都過了  我們最好快點忘掉
I think we'll all be better off when we get past it.
是啊  但是你比一般人都..
Yeah, but you really went beyond what the average...
我想要  我想要和我的家人呆在一起
l... I need to... I really need to be with my family.
謝謝
Thanks.
我是珍尼·懷亞特  這就是湯姆·史多
I'm Jenny Wyatt in Millbrook, and that was Tom Stall...
一個不善言辭的美國民族英雄
American hero, man of few words.
好了  我想我們已經採訪夠了
Well, I guess that's all we're going to get.
回家的感覺真是好了
Man, it's good to be home.
我希望不會再有更多的這類事情了
I hope there won't be too much more of that.
嘿 爸爸 他們只想採訪你
Hey, Dad, they all just want to interview you...
因為你做了這些事情
because of what you did.
你真個英雄 爸爸
You're a hero, Dad. Ha ha!
不 我不是
No, I'm not.
我只是運氣好  運氣很好
I just got lucky... very lucky.
當他們發現更新更火的新聞時
This will all blow over...
這一切就會結束
as soon as they find some other hot story.
是啊  說不定下個新聞就是萊頓發現了雙頭怪牛
Yeah. Maybe the Lydons will have another two-headed cow.
你們的想像力還不夠豐富
You guys aren't thinking big enough.
爸爸 你該去做Larry King Live(美國CNN電視採訪節目)
You could probably do Larry Klng Llve, Dad.
- 那就酷極了  - 噢 夠了 別說了
- That would be cool. - Oh, you stop it. Stop it.
看看 更多的記者
Look at this... more reporters.
他們還在哪裡嗎?
Are they still there?
是啊  街對面停了些車
Yeah. Now there's some car parked across the road.
- 他們就坐在那裡  - 恩
- They're just sitting there. - Huh.
- 有人想喝茶嗎?  - 我想喝 媽媽
- Does anyone want some tea? - I'll take some, Mom.
我也要
Yes, please.
敖  天哪
Unh. Aw, jeez.
嘿  伊迪
Hey, Edie.
嗨  你好嗎?
Hi. How are you?
- 你去商店了嗎?  - 是的
- Did you go to the shop? - Yes, sir.
你好 嘿 比利
Hello. Hey, Bill.
- 嗨 親愛的  - 嗨 親愛的 你好嗎?
- Hi, honey. - Hi, baby. How are you?
噢  我還好  什麼風把你吹過來了?
Oh, I'm all right. What brings you by?
我只是想過來看看你怎麼樣
I just wanted to see how you were doing.
很好  生意好極了  我都忙不過來了
Doing good. Business is great. Just can't keep up.
是啊  人真多
Yeah, it's busy.
噢  看  更多的記者  真不錯
Oh, look, more reporters. Nice.
他們看起來不像記者
They don't look like reporters.
烤乳酪好了
Grilled cheese is ready.
拿著薯條和草莓搖搖樂
Got fries and a strawberry shake.
你好  歡迎來到史多小店
Hello. Welcome to Stall's.
你們來些咖啡嗎?
Would you gentlemen like some coffee?
你就是那個英雄
You're the hero.
呃  先生  我不知道  我只是
Uh, I don't know, sir. I was just...
不  你就是那個大英雄
Nah, you're the big hero.
你制服了那兩個壞人
You sure took care of those two bad men.
先生 我真的不想再談這個事情了
I really don't like talking about it, sir.
我們只是想回到原來的樣子
We're trying to get back to normal here.
那麼 你們喝咖啡嗎?
So, can I offer you gentlemen some coffee?
當然  我要咖啡  黑咖啡
Sure. Give me some coffee. Make it black...
- 好的  先生  - 喬依
- Yes, sir. - Joey.
那你的朋友要些什麼?
And... and your friends?
他們不喝咖啡
They don't drink coffee.
他們不適合喝咖啡  喬依
It doesn't agree with them... Joey.
- 誰是喬依?  - 你就是
- Who's Joey? - You are.
- 先生我的名字叫 湯姆  - 是的
- My name's Tom, sir. - Of course it is.
咖啡真不錯
Mmm. That's good coffee.
謝謝你的讚賞 先生
Thank you, sir.
我在費城的時候就在尋找這麼好的咖啡
If I were to find coffee as good in Philadelphia...
你也知道  對嗎?  湯姆
but you know that, don't you, Tom?
不  實際上我不知道  我從來沒去過費城
No, actually, I don't. I've never been to Philadelphia.
賓夕法尼亞州? 你們是從那裡來的嗎?
Pennsylvania? Is that where you gentlemen are from?
是啊  就像你不知道一樣
Yeah, like you don't know.
不好意思  我們  我們認識嗎?
Sorry. Did... Did we know each other?
該你告訴我
You tell me.
不
No.
我們不認識
We don't know each other.
喬依 別說廢話了
Come on, Joey. Cut the crap.
我的名字叫湯姆
My name is Tom.
喬依·崔瑟克  你的名字叫喬依·崔瑟克
Joey Cusack. Your name is Joey Cusack.
你是費城人
You're from Philly.
- 呃  隨便吧
- Mm-hmm. OK. Whatever. - Uh-huh.
先生  不好意思  如果你們不打算點東西的話
Excuse me, gentlemen, if you're not going to order anything...
我和我的丈夫希望
my husband and I would appreciate it...
你們自己離開
if you would be on your way.
我們在路上已經吃過了
We ate on the road.
沒什麼
It's all right.
沒關係
It's OK.
正如你所看到的  今天我們這裡的生意很忙
We really are very busy here today, as you can see.
如果你們幾位先生不準備吃東西的話
Um, so if you gentlemen aren't going to be eating...
我更情願把這些座位提供給在這裡消費的顧客
I really should offer your seats to paying customers.
好吧
Well...
現在  我們也是在這裡消費的顧客了
now we're paying customers.
我不能收
I can't take this.
這對你來說沒什麼問題吧?
It shouldn't be any problem for you.
這是怎麼意思呢?
What is that supposed to mean?
弗加特先生只是在裡談談話
Mr. Fogarty's just making conversation here.
好吧 不管你們叫什麼
Well, whatever you want to call it...
談話到此結束
this conversation is over.
弗加特先生  我認為他是想讓我們離開
I think he wants us to leave, Mr. Fogarty.
弗加特先生 你知道嗎?
Do you know what he does...
他不喜歡別人在這裡的時候  他會做些什麼
when he don't like people, Mr. Fogarty?
是的  我很害怕
Yeah. I'm scared.
我們該在他折磨我們之前離開這裡
We should leave before he goes all Dirty Harry on us.
喬依  謝謝你的咖啡
I want to thank you for the coffee, Joey.
非常的好喝
It really is very good.
湯姆  我的名字叫湯姆·史多
It's Tom. My name's Tom Stall.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你在幹什麼?  你在給誰打電話?
What are you doing? Who are you calling?
嗨  嗨  茉莉  我是伊迪·史多  他在嗎?
Hi... Hi, Molly. This is Edie Stall. Is he in?
我很好 謝謝
I'm fine, thanks.
你在給薩姆打電話?
You're calling Sam?
是的
Yes.
警官  我開車有問題嗎?
Is there a problem with my driving, officer?
先生  能給我看一下你的駕照嗎?
Can I see your license, sir?
沒問題
Sure.
我沒有超速
I thought I was under the limit.
有什麼問題我能知道嗎?
Is there some problem I should know about?
先生 你們到密爾布盧克來幹什麼?
What's your business in Millbrook, sir?
我們是來旅遊的
We're tourists.
你們今天在史多的餐館裡幹什麼?
And what business did you have at Stall's Diner today?
我們聽說那裡的咖啡真是棒極了
We heard the coffee was terrific.
有些事情我要給你和莫里根先生講清楚
Let me make something clear to you and to Mr. Mulligan.
恩?
Uh-huh?
這裡是個美麗的小鎮
This is a nice town.
我們這裡的人也很善良
We have nice people here.
我們會保護善良的人們
We take care of our nice people.
- 你明白了嗎?  - 是的 當然
- Do you understand me? - Yeah, sure.
不要讓我在這附近再看到你們
Don't let me see you around again.
你的工作做的很好 警官
You keep up the good work, officer.
查裡斯·羅克  來自費城
Charles Roarke, Philadelphia.
和三宗謀殺案有關
Indicted on three counts of murder.
弗蘭克·莫里根  來自紐約
Frank Mulligan, out of New York...
和1宗謀殺案有關
indicted on one count of murder.
涉嫌和另外幾起罪名有關
Questioned in relation to dozens of acts of violence...
這些都是你們不想聽到的
that you don't want to hear about.
這兩個人都為卡爾·弗加特賣命
Both men work for Carl Fogarty.
就是那個眼睛有問題的傢伙
He's the fella with the eye.
他由於犯過很多襲擊罪 在監獄裡服刑15年
He spent fifteen years in prison on several counts of assault.
他涉嫌和6宗命案有關
He's suspected in half a dozen murders...
以及多起失蹤案
and more disappearances.
湯姆 這些人是來自東海岸的集團化罪犯
Tom, these guys are organized crime from the east coast.
他們來真的  他們不是好人
Now, they're the real thing. They're bad men.
上帝啊  上帝啊  親愛的
Jesus. Jesus, honey.
我想問你一個問題
I have to ask you a question.
你是不是在做一些案件的污點證人?
Are you in some kind of witness protection plan?
- 薩姆  - 一些什麼?
- Sam. - Some kind of what?
我沒搞笑  伊迪
This is no laughing matter, Edie.
他當然沒有  薩姆
Of course he's not, Sam.
我希望聽他自己說
I'd just like to hear Tom say that.
好吧  沒有  我沒有去做污點證人
OK. No. No, I'm not in a witness program.
他們只是認錯了人
Those men just have the wrong guy.
我猜他們看到我在電視上
They must've seen me on TV, and I guess, uh...
我讓他們想了一個叫喬尼的人
I reminded them of this Johnny guy.
- 喬依  - 喬依這個人
- Joey. - J-Joey somebody.
我  我的上帝啊  我的想法....
I mean, good lord. The idea of me...
我也不相信  但是我要問清楚
I never honestly believed it, but I had to ask.
我對喬依·崔瑟克這個人做了點研究
I've done some research on this, uh, Joey Cusack.
但是我沒找到任何的線索
I didn't find anything.
但是在費城有一個叫瑞奇·崔瑟克的人
But there is a Richie Cusack in Philadelphia.
很顯然  他就是那個
Apparently, he's the head...
犯罪集團的首腦
of some kind of crime syndicate in that city.
這些人來到我們的小鎮來騷擾我們這裡的居民
Men like this come to our town and start harassing a citizen...
我們必須嚴肅的對待這件事情
we have to take them seriously.
當然
Sure.
好的  如果你們看到他們來了的話
All right. So, if you folks see them coming around...
你們就告訴我
you let me know.
我們會的
Will do.
不好意思 薩母 你想來一塊派或是其他的什麼東西嗎?
I'm sorry, Sam. Do you want a piece of pie or something?
噢  不了  謝謝  伊迪
Ah, no, thanks, Edie.
我想吃  但是我必須要回去工作
I'd love to, but I've gotta get back to work.
謝謝你來我們這裡
Thank you. Thanks for coming.
薩姆?  謝謝
Uh, Sam? Thank you.
你能保護我們  我們太高興了
It's good to know you're watching out for us.
別客氣  湯姆
Come on, Tom.
你知道負責這裡的安全是我們的工作
You know we look out for our own here.
- 晚安  - 晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
回見  謝謝
See ya. Thanks.
別擔心
Don't worry.
他們已經離開這裡了
They're as good as gone.
對不起  對不起
Sorry. Sorry.
一切都過去了
It's over and done with.
好的
OK.
親愛的  你能接電話嗎  親愛的?
Honey. Can you get that, hon?
接啊  接啊
Come on, come on!
喂?
Hello?
鳥槍 伊迪  快拿鳥槍
The shotgun, Edie! Get the shotgun!
湯姆  湯姆  湯姆  怎麼了?
Tom, Tom... Tom, what's wrong?
他們朝家的方向來了
They're coming to the house!
誰朝家裡來了?
Who's coming to the house?
快去拿  照我說的做  快準備好
Just grab it! Do it and be ready!
好的  停  你說真的嗎?
OK, stop. Are you serious?
我儘快趕回來
I'll be there as soon as I can.
媽的
Shit.
快啊
Come on.
噢  媽的
Oh, shit.
噢  快
Oh, come on.
快 快
Come on.
伊迪  噢
Edie! Oh.
噢  媽的  湯姆
Ohh, fuck. Tom!
湯姆  湯姆  到底怎麼了?
Tom. Tom, what's going on?
- 我  - 啊?
- L... - Huh?
我...我不知道  親愛的
L... I don't know, baby.
上帝啊
Jesus.
怎麼了?
What's going on?
我不... 我不知道 噢
I don't... I don't know. Ohh.
讓我打電話給薩姆  行嗎?
Let me call Sam, all right?
- 不  不要了  - 好吧
- No, don't. - OK.
我  我甚至不知道
L... I don't even know...
我  我不知道  為什麼我想  我
l... I don't know why I thought... l...
媽媽?
Mom?
好了  沒什麼  乖乖
It's OK, baby.
呃  哈  哈
Yeah. Uh... ha ha. L...
我  我  我覺得  我快瘋了
l... l... I think I'm losing my mind.
不  不  不  好了  你沒瘋
No, no, no. OK. You're not losing your mind.
你只是受了些傷  好了
You've been through some serious trauma, all right?
我在這裡陪你  我這裡陪你  親愛的
I'm here for you, baby. We're all here for you.
好了  好了 一切都好了
It's all right. It's gonna be OK.
媽媽?
Mom?
你沒忘了我鞋子的事情吧?
You haven't forgotten about my new shoes, have you?
天哪  當然沒有  那是我今天要做的第1件事
Gosh, no. It's my top priority for the day.
我怎麼可能忘記呢?  你還好吧?
How could I forget? You all right?
是啊  是的  嗨  乖乖
Yeah, yeah. Hi... Hi, sweetie.
親愛的  準備好去上學
Honey, just get ready for school.
我晚點再告訴你  好嗎?
I'll speak to you afterwards, all right?
好的
OK.
走吧
Come on.
我們去買東西
Let's go shopping.
當心點  上了膛的
Careful. It's loaded.
為什麼媽媽拿著槍在家裡到處跑?
Why was Mom running around the house with that?
發生了什麼事情?  爸爸
What's going on, Dad?
假警報
False alarm.
沒什麼好擔心的
Nothing to worry about.
我很擔心
I am worried.
你滿身大汗  你濕透了  爸爸
You're sweating. You're soaked, Dad.
哪種假警報?
What kind of false alarm?
你剛才說的什麼意思?  你說你
What did you mean, you think you...
你覺得你快瘋掉了?
You think you're losing your mind?
餐館有一些暴徒
Some mob guys showed up at the diner.
他們在電視上看到我 他們專門過來看下我到底什麼樣子
They saw me on TV, and they came by to take a look at me.
是嗎?
Yeah.
是的  我聽說了  呃  所以
Yeah, I heard about that. Uh, so...
他們覺得他們認識我
They thought they knew me.
他們把我認成了另外的人
They thought... I was somebody else.
嘿  真是怪異
Heh. That's weird.
是啊  夠怪的
Yeah. Weird.
我猜  呃  我猜
And I guess, um... Well, I guess...
他們不喜歡這樣的人  他們認為你就是這樣的人
they don't like this guy they think you are.
明顯不是
Apparently not.
我覺得  呃
And, um, and I guess l...
我猜  他們想
I guess... I guess they want...
他們想殺了這個人  你就是這個人?
to kill this guy they think you are?
是的  這個就快讓我瘋掉的原因
See, that's... that's the losing my mind part.
我的意思是  我沒理由那樣想
I mean, I have no reason to think that.
我只是想工作  你也知道
It's just I was down at work, and, you know...
突然  我想可能  可能是
suddenly I thought maybe... maybe...
他們只是過來看看而已
they'd come looking around.
你明白嗎?
You know?
呃
And, uh...
你急急忙忙地跑回來救我們?
And then you came running back here to save us?
是啊  一些愚蠢的想法
Yeah, something silly like that.
我十分抱歉
I'm sorry.
如果你是正確的呢
What if you're right?
我們就只有面對
Then we deal with it.
看我找到了什麼?
Now, look what I just found.
這種款式的最後一雙  剛好合你的尺碼
It's my last pair in this style, and it's exactly your size.
穿上試試  做夢都找不到這麼合適的
Just try these on. They should fit like a dream.
感覺怎麼樣?
How do they feel?
很好 謝謝  我很喜歡
Good. Yeah, I think I like them.
我自己也有一雙
I have a pair of these myself.
真的很不錯  但真的也是最後一雙了
They look great and they really last.
是嗎?  好的我買下了
Really? OK. I'll take them.
我還需要給她賣一雙
And I needed a pair for her as well.
莎拉
Sarah?
- 呃  女士 這鞋子  - 我要找我的女兒
- Uh, ma'am? The shoes... - I have to find my daughter.
我不能讓你把鞋子穿出商店
I can't let you leave the store with the shoes.
好的  好的  好的  莎拉
OK, OK, OK. Sarah!
莎拉
Sarah?
莎拉  莎拉  以後別在這樣了
Sarah. Sarah. Don't ever do that again, OK?
對不起  媽媽
I'm sorry, Mommy.
但你看  這裡有新款式的摩托車娃娃
But look. They have the new Vespa dolls.
沒什麼好擔心的  史多夫人
Nothin' to worry about, Mrs. Stall.
我一直看著她呢
I've been watching over her.
你他媽的離我的家人遠一點  你這個狗娘養的
You stay the fuck away from my family, you son of a bitch.
沒必要用這樣的詞語吧  史多夫人
There's no need for that kind of language, Mrs. Stall.
我告訴你  我不知道你想要什麼
Listen to me. I don't know what you want...
但我也不想知道
and I don't really care.
你應該關心我想要的東西  史多夫人
You should care about what I want, Mrs. Stall...
因為我想要從丈夫那裡得到一些東西
because I want something from your husband...
那會影響你  甚至改變你的生活
that might affect you, might change your life.
我的丈夫不認識你
My husband does not know you.
他不會認識像你這樣的人
He wouldn't know you, somebody like you.
噢  他認識卡爾·弗加特  知道嗎?
Oh, he knows Carl Fogarty, all right.
他對我再熟悉不過了
He knows me intimately.
看到了嗎?  這只眼睛沒有完全的瞎
See? This isn't a completely dead eye.
還可以看到一點
It still works a bit.
問題是 我用這只眼睛能看到的唯一的東西
The problem is, the only thing I can see with it...
就是  喬依·崔瑟克
is Joey Cusack.
能把他看穿
And it can see right through him.
能看穿你的丈夫  伊迪
Right through your husband, Edie.
看看他心裡到底怎麼了?  什麼讓他這麼規矩
See what's inside him, what makes him tick.
那還是原來那個人
He's still the same guy.
- 不  - 他還是以前那個瘋狂的喬依
- No. - He's still crazy fuckin' Joey.
你也知道  不是嗎?
And you know it, don't you?
我所知道是  我的丈夫是湯姆·史多
I know that my husband is Tom Stall. That's what I know.
- 是嗎?  - 是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
好啊  你怎麼不問問湯姆一些關於他哥哥瑞奇的事情?
Well, why don't you ask Tom about his older brother Richie?
他不....
He doesn't...
問問湯姆是怎麼用帶刺的鐵絲網把我的眼睛弄瞎的
Ask Tom about how he tried to rip my eye out with barbed wire.
問問他  伊迪
And ask him, Edie...
他是如何這麼會殺人的?
how come he's so good at killing people?
如果讓我看到你在我5英尺之內
If I see you within five hundred feet of me...
或者是我的孩子和丈夫  我就只有讓你被抓起來
or my children or my husband, I'll have you arrested.
哼  哼  哼  哼  哼  哼
Heh heh heh heh.
我還能對你講的再清楚一點嗎?
Can I possibly make myself any clearer than that?
不  不  史多夫人  你不會的  謝謝你給我這麼多時間
No, no, Mrs. Stall, you can't. I thank you for your time.
你有個可愛的女兒
You have an enchanting daughter.
還有  史多夫人
And, Mrs. Stall...
別忘了你的鞋子
don't forget your shoes.
哼 哼 哼 哼 哼 哼
Heh heh heh heh.
你爸爸怎麼樣了?
So, how's your dad?
我不知道  有點怪怪的
I don't know. A little weird.
是啊  在他經歷了那麼多以後
Well, after what he went through?
我是說  真的殺掉一個人
I mean, actually killing someone?
這足以讓任何一個人瘋掉
I mean, that's enough to freak anybody out.
是啊  我也覺得
Yeah. I guess.
你爸是條硬漢  對吧?
So, your old man's some kind of tough guy, huh?
他怎麼想他這個懦弱的兒子呢?
What's he think of his wimp son?
你覺得他能接受嗎?
You think he'd take this shit? You think he'd make jokes?
繼續啊  混蛋  說點好笑的啊
Go on, bitch. Say something funny.
博比  別這樣
Bobby, leave him alone.
閉嘴 斯刊克
Shut up, skank.
啊噢  他要發瘋了
Uh-oh. He's gettin' mad.
傑克 我們出去吧  好嗎?
Jack, let's just get out of here, OK?
傑克  他是個混蛋  你知道的
Jack, he's an asshole. You know that.
他沒什麼其他的意思  我們走吧
He doesn't mean shit. Let's just go.
我們出去吧  好嗎?
Let's just get out of here, OK?
是啊  女人  快跑啊
Yeah, puss. Run away.
我敢打賭你的爸爸因你而感到恥辱
Goddamn, I bet your daddy would be real ashamed by you.
來啊  混蛋  說點好玩的啊
Go ahead, bitch. Say something funny.
讓我笑笑
Make me laugh.
- 啊  - 噢
- Uhh! - Ohh!
好啊  你這個他媽的傻瓜  過來  你這個狗娘養的
OK, you motherfucker! Get over there, you son of a bitch!
過來  你在笑嗎?
Come here. Are you laughin'?
你現在在笑嗎?
Are you laughin' now...
你他媽的混蛋
you motherfucking cocksucking piece of shit?
你到底在想些什麼?
What the hell were you thinking?
- 我沒想  - 當然沒想
- I wasn't thinking. - Obviously not.
博比幾年來一直騎在我頭上  爸爸  他是個混球
Bobby's been riding me all year, Dad. He's a jerk.
他是個混球?
He's a jerk?
是的  他是個混球
Yeah. He's a jerk.
不要找藉口  你打了他
That's no excuse. You stand up to him.
就差點沒把他送進醫院
You don't put him in the hospital!
噢 沒什麼大不了的
Oh, big deal.
隨便誰打了他都是一件好事
It's the best thing anyone could've done to him.
再說了  我只是被停課了而已
Besides, I only got suspended.
這個事情夠大了
It Is a big deal!
他父母說要起訴我們
His parents say they might sue us.
可以被告成蓄意傷人
There could be assault charges.
我們負擔不起  傑克
We can't afford that, Jack.
我們沒那麼多錢
We don't have that kind of money.
噢  什麼?  媽媽不會接這個案子?
Oh, what? Mom's not gonna take the case?
- 噢  不管什麼  爸爸  - 聽著 會說的小子
- Oh, whatever, Dad... - Listen, smart mouth!
我們家裡我們解決問題不靠打人
In this family, we do not solve our problems by hitting people!
不  在這個家裡  我們只拿槍殺人
No, in this family, we shoot them!
傑克
Jack.
親愛的  你看到傑克了嗎?
Honey, have you seen Jack?
怎麼了?
What?
親愛的  怎麼了?
What's wrong, baby?
弗加特和他的手下跟蹤我們到了商場
Fogarty and his men followed us to the mall.
他怎麼?
He what?
打電話給薩姆  我們該打電話找他嗎?
Call Sam. Should... Should we call Sam?
我們應該要打電話
We should call...
我已經解決了這件事情了  親愛的
I already took care of it, honey.
我已經解決了這個事情了  我去了法院
I already took care of it. Went down to the courthouse...
拿到了逮捕令
got a restraining order.
那會起很大的作用
A lot of good that'll do.
恩  只能這樣了
Well, it's something.
至少我們能逮捕他
At least we could have him arrested...
如果他再在這個附近出現
if he ever comes around here again.
你是對的
You're right.
但是我要告訴你一些事情
But I have to tell you something.
什麼?
What?
這個叫弗加特的人始終認為
This man Fogarty really believes...
你就是喬依·崔瑟克
that you're this Joey Cusack.
我是說  他今天下午告訴我的事情
I mean, the things that he told me this afternoon...
- 什麼事情?  - 那些事情  都是胡說的
- What things? - Things. Just bullshit.
但是他很肯定你就是那個人
But he's, uh, he's sure that it's you.
我們必須要讓他相信你不是他說的那個人
And we have to convince him that it's not.
我覺得他是不是對檢測我的DNA有興趣?
Well, I don't think he's interested in examining my DNA.
放下你的武器
Get off our property.
喬依 我們走吧
We'll go, Joey.
我們只是你想和我們一起走
We just want you to come with us.
回費城去見一些人
Come back to Philly, see some people.
我告訴過你  我沒有去過費城
I told you, I have never been to Philadelphia.
呵  你自己都相信你的廢話?
Heh. You almost believe your own crap, don't you?
你這麼辛苦的裝成這個人
You know, you're trying so hard to be this other guy.
看起來真痛苦
It's painful to watch.
- 查理  - 是的
- Charlie. - Hey.
看看我們找到了什麼
Look what we found.
出來
Come on.
耶!  哈  哈  哈  哈
Yeah? Ha ha ha.
- 媽媽  - 傑克
- Mom! - Jack!
- 不要  伊迪 伊迪  - 媽媽
- No! Edie! Edie! - Mom!
- 伊迪 不 不要  - 傑克
- Edie! No! No! - Jack!
讓我走  你這個混蛋
Let go, you son of a bitch!
過來
Come here.
等等
Wait.
媽媽
Mom.
喬依  不要讓我們傷害孩子
Don't make us hurt the kid, Joey.
我只想你和我們一起旅行一下
We just want you to come for a little trip with us...
沿著記憶之路
down Memory Lane.
放下你的玩具槍  過來和我們談談
Put the popgun down. Come over and talk to us.
親愛的  等等
Baby, wait.
伊迪  我去把他接回來
Edie... I will get him.
我去  求你了
I'll get him. Please.
去照顧莎拉
Go up to Sarah.
去照顧莎拉  去吧
Go up to her. Do it.
放下搶
Put the gun down.
放下槍  喬依
Put it down, Joey.
走近點
Come closer.
再過來點
A little further.
來吧
Come on.
傑克  回屋去
Go back to the house, Jack.
去吧
Go on.
你看  當你決定合作的時候一切事情都好辦了
You see how cozy it can be when you decide to play nice?
來吧  喬依  上車吧
Now, come on, Joey. Get in the car.
你不用帶牙刷  我們一切為你準備好了
You won't need your toothbrush. We'll take care of everything.
我覺得你如果現在離開的話會更好點
I think it'd be better if you'd just leave now.
喬依
Joey.
來吧  喬依  我們走吧
Come on, Joey, let's go.
- 啊  - 啊
- Uhh! - Uhh! Uhh!
噢  噢
Ohh! Ohh!
湯姆
Tom!
媽的
Fuck.
媽媽  怎麼了?
Mommy, what's wrong?
沒什麼
It's OK.
你死之前還有什麼好說的嗎?
You got anything to say before I blow your brains out...
你這個可憐蟲
you miserable prick?
我當時在費城的時候就該殺了你
I should've killed you back in Philly.
是啊  喬依
Yeah, Joey.
你該的
You should have.
啊  啊
Uhh! Uhh.
伊迪
Edie.
親愛的  你還好嗎?
Honey, are you OK?
告訴我真相
Tell me the truth.
真相?
The truth?
求求你了  告訴我好嗎?
Please. You can do that, can't you?
告訴我好嗎?  求求你了
You can do that, can't you? Please?
你聽到了什麼嗎?
What do you think you heard?
不是我聽到的
It's not what I heard.
是我看到的
It's what I saw.
我看到了喬依
I saw Joey.
我看到你在我眼前變成了喬依
I saw you turn into Joey right before my eyes.
我看到了一個殺人魔  弗加特警告過我
I saw a killer... the one Fogarty warned me about.
你在費城殺過人  對嗎?
You did kill men back in Philly, didn't you?
你是不是為了錢才那樣做
Did you do it for money...
或者是你只是因為  因為你喜歡殺人?
or did you do it because you enjoyed it?
都是喬依做的 不是我
Joey did, both. I didn't...
湯姆·史多不會這樣做
Tom Stall didn't.
噢  我的上帝
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
噢  我的天啊  這一切是真的
Oh, God, it's really happening.
你到底是什麼?  得了多重人格分裂症?
What are you, like, some multiple personality schizoid?
這些對你來說就像來來回回得開關電閘一樣簡單?
It's like flipping a switch back and forth for you?
我也不想再看見那個喬依
I never expected to see Joey again.
噢  是啊  喬依
Oh, yeah. Joey.
那他在躲什麼嗎?  還是他死了?
What, was he in hiding? Was he dead?
我想是這樣的
I thought he was.
我想我已經不是喬依·崔瑟克了
I thought I killed Joey Cusack.
我在沙漠死裡逃生的時候之後  我就不再是他了
I went out to the desert, and I killed him.
噢  我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我用了三年的時間變成了湯姆·史多
I spent three years becoming Tom Stall.
伊迪  這些事情你應該知道
Edie, you have to know this.
我遇到了你以後才如獲重生
I wasn't really born again until I met you.
我什麼都不是
I was nothing.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
我不敢相信這發生的一切
I can't believe this is happening.
我不敢相信他媽的這一切居然發生了
I can't believe this is fucking happening!
你不是在波蘭長大的
You didn't grow up in Portland.
你從來也沒提過你的養父母
And you never talk about your adopted parents...
因為你壓根就沒有
because you don't have any!
我們的名字
And our name.
我的天  我的名字
Jesus Christ, my name.
傑克的名字  莎拉的名字
Jack's name. Sarah's name?
史多?  湯姆·史多?
Stall? Tom Stall?
你亂編的嗎?
Did you just make that up?
這個名字從哪裡來的?
Where did that name come from?
我的意思是
I mean...
這個名字剛好可以用
it was available.
是啊
Yeah.
我猜我也是剛好可以用  對吧?
I guess I was available, too.
嘿  傑克
Hey, Jack.
我現在該叫你什麼?
What am I supposed to call you now?
你該叫我爸爸
You're supposed to call me Dad.
我就是  你的爸爸
That's what I am... your dad.
真的嗎?
Are you really?
那種犯罪集團裡的爸爸?
So, you're some kind of closet mobster dad?
如果我搶劫了米里肯藥店的話
I mean, if I go rob Millikan's Drug Store...
你會因為這個事情打我嗎?
will you ground me if I don't give you a piece of the action?
是嗎?  爸爸  告訴我
What, Dad? You tell me.
別這樣  孩子
Please, son. Don't.
如果我把你的事情給薩姆說了  你還會打我嗎?
If I talk to Sam about you, will you have me whacked?
傑克
Jack.
湯姆?
Tom?
嘿  薩姆  今天怎麼樣?
Hey, Sam. How are you doing?
看到你康復了  我真是高興
Good to see you up and around.
- 是啊  - 你能讓它跑起來了嗎?
- Yeah. - You had her runnin' yet?
是啊  還要等段時間
Yeah, for a second there.
它就可以活過來了
She's coming back to life.
噢  媽的
Ah, shit.
湯姆
Tom...
我有個問題
I got a problem.
進去坐坐?
Want to come inside for a minute?
我這幾天都在想這個問題
I've been running through it all for the last couple days.
我覺的這個事情不太合理
It just doesn't fit.
什麼不合理?
What doesn't fit?
什麼都不合理
None of it.
是伊迪回來了嗎?
Is that Edie coming home?
是的
Yeah.
好吧  我們現在先不說這個
Well, we don't have to do this now.
那最好
Might as well.
嗨  薩姆
Hi, Sam.
伊迪
Edie.
你好嗎?
How you doing?
我很好
I'm OK.
來點咖啡嗎?
You want some coffee?
不  我不要
No, I'm good.
那麼  什麼風把你吹過來了?
So, what brings you out here?
我和湯姆剛才在說那件事情
Well, Tom and I were just talking about that.
我也想聽聽
Mmm. I'd like to hear it.
好吧  只是
Well, it's just that...
我所說的不代表什麼意思
none of this makes any sense.
這些人都是些偷偷摸摸的人
These are serious secretive men.
我是說  他們不會跑到這裡來
I mean, they wouldn't have come out here...
他們不會跑到這裡來這樣做
they wouldn't have gone through all this...
來暴露他們自己
exposed themselves like this...
除非是他們認定了他們找到了他們要找的那個人
unless they were dead certain they had the right man.
那麼 你到底想說什麼?  薩姆
So, what are you saying, Sam?
我只是說  我想知道真相
I'm saying I think I need to hear the truth.
真相?
The truth?
是的  真相
The truth.
薩姆 你的時間比較充裕
Sam, you've got too much time on your hands.
什麼?
I'm sorry?
湯姆是
Tom is...
湯姆就是他自己
Tom is who he says he is.
就是這個意思
That's all that really matters.
薩姆  我們這個家遭遇的事情還不夠多嗎?
Sam, hasn't this family suffered enough?
好吧
Well...
真該死
goddamn.
伊迪
Edie.
好了
It's OK.
我想我該走了
I guess I'll be going.
如果你們需要什麼?明  給我打個電話就是
You folks give me a ring if you need anything.
隨便什麼事情  明白了嗎?
Anything at all, understand?
謝謝
Thanks.
你
You...
伊迪  伊迪
Edie. Edie!
- 離我遠點  - 啊
- Get off of me! - Unh!
去你媽的  喬依
Fuck you, Joey!
啊  走開
Aah! Get off!
我的天啊  我的天啊
Oh, my God. Oh, God.
喂
Hello.
嘿  我的兄弟
Hey, bro-ham.
你仍然還是那麼會殺人
You're still pretty good with the killing.
真是刺激
That's exciting.
瑞奇
Richie.
對啊  我是瑞奇  你有什麼要說的嗎?  喬依
Yeah, it's Richie. What do you say, Joey?
是你來看看我?
Are you going to come see me?
還是我來看看你?
Or do I have to come see you?
那應該是什麼意思?
What's that supposed to mean?
呃  Jenny Cream (酒名)
Uh, Jenny Cream.
一瓶
Bottle.
你是魯本?
You Ruben?
是的
Yeah.
你是喬依?
You Joey?
是的  我是喬依
Yeah, I'm Joey.
我們現在做什麼?
So, what do we do now?
你先喝完你的啤酒
You finish your beer...
然後我帶你到艾斯卡拉德去見瑞奇
then I take you to see Richie in the Escalade.
房子不錯
Nice houses.
瑞奇可是那種高層次的人
Richie's a very upscale kind of guy.
門也不錯
Nice gate.
是啊
Yeah.
我們到了
We're here.
家  溫馨的家
Home, sweet home.
我們要搜一下身
Got to frisk you.
不用了  別麻煩了
Nah. I'll save you the trouble.
我什麼都沒帶
I'm not packing.
我們要搜一下身
I got to frisk you.
好吧
All right.
我身上不怎麼好聞
I don't smell very good.
我開了很久的車  沒停過
I've been driving pretty much non-stop...
15到16的小時的樣子
fifteen to sixteen hours.
我會捏住鼻子
I'll hold my nose.
你還相信那個叫Track & Turf的酒吧還在繼續營業嗎?
Can you believe that place is still standing the Track and Turf?
你沒調戲那個叫吉利·立維的女人嗎?
Didn't you bang Jill Levy there...
就在吧臺上  就在大家的面前
right on the bar in front of everybody?
我從來沒調戲過吉利·立維
I never banged Jill Levy.
你該那樣的  她還有點意思
Well, you should've. She was... She was something.
近來可好?  瑞奇
How you doing, Richie?
不錯
Yeah.
很久  很久沒看到你了
It's been a long, long time, bro-ham.
- 是啊  - 是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.
跟我來
Come with me.
- 你想吃點什麼嗎?  - 不了
- You want anything? - Nah.
你喜歡那樣的田園生活?
So, you like that farm life?
擠牛奶  清理糞便?
Milking cows and shit?
我沒什麼農莊
I don't have a farm.
沒有?
No?
弗加特覺得你好象就是生活在那種農莊裡
Fogarty thought you lived on some kind of farm.
還說可以聞到豬的味道
Said you could smell pig.
他怎麼可能知道
How that old fart would know...
豬聞起來像什麼  我也不知道
what a pig smells like, I don't know...
但他就那樣說
but that's what he said.
你喜歡結婚嗎?
Do you like being married?
什麼?
What?
你喜歡結婚嗎?
Do you like being married?
對你來說不錯吧?
Does it work for you?
對我來說就行不通
I can't see it working for me.
我從來沒有想結婚的欲望
I never felt the urge, you know?
世界上那麼多漂亮的女人
A lot of great looking women in the world.
我從來沒有遇到哪個女人可以讓我放棄其他的女人
I never met one made me want to give up all the others.
當然了 你可以到處風流
Sure, you can fuck around...
還有很多的事情可以做
but it's so much goddamn work, you know?
然後回家什麼都不說
Keeping it quiet.
那樣不值得
It's not worth the effort.
別那樣做
Don't see the upside.
你那樣做了嗎 喬依?
You see the upside, Joey?
是的 瑞奇
Yeah, Richie, I do.
我現在就是
I do now.
兄弟 你讓我很生氣
I'm pretty pissed at you, bro-ham.
你該打個電話給我
You could've called.
或者是寄張明信片來給我
You could've dropped a postcard in the mail.
我們是兄弟  你覺得會怎麼樣?
We're brothers. What'd you think would happen?
我覺得我們該先說正事
I thought that business would come first.
好吧
Well, yeah.
是的  我知道
Yeah, I know.
我知道
Tch. I know.
我該怎麼辦?
What am I going to do?
你惹到了一些有勢力的人
You bust up a made man's place.
你殺了他幾個手下
You killed some of his guys.
你還弄瞎了他的眼睛
You take his eye.
上帝啊  你弄瞎了他的眼睛
Jesus, Joey, you took his eye.
用帶刺的鐵絲網  是嗎?
Barbed wire, wasn't it?
太糟糕了  你總是那個最瘋狂的人
That's disgusting. You always were the crazy one.
- 再也不是了  - 是的  我聽說了
- Not anymore. - Yeah, I heard.
你生活在你的春秋大夢裡
You're living the American dream.
你已經開始做夢了 是嗎?
You really bought into it, didn't you?
你做原來的你那麼久了
You've been this other guy...
現在也用了一樣的時間變成了那個人
almost as long as you've been yourself.
嘿 你在做夢的時候
Hey, when you dream...
你還是喬依嗎?
are you still Joey?
喬依已經死了很久了
Joey's been dead a long time.
但你現在還坐在這裡
And yet here you sit...
沒什麼區別
big as life.
你要知道 你讓我花費了
You know you cost me...
大量的時間和金錢
a lot of time and money.
在你殺掉弗加特之前
Before you pulled that shit with Fogarty...
我本來是要成為下一任老大的
I was a shoe-in to take over...
而且是內定的
when the boss croaked... a shoe-in.
我說的很清楚了  喬依
It was made very clear to me, Joey.
我不得不去收拾你留下的爛攤子
I had to clean up your mess...
還要解決一些我從來沒遇到過的事情
or nothing was ever going to happen for me.
你根本不知道
You got no idea how much shit I had to pull...
我是怎麼才讓那些人不來找我麻煩的
to get back in with those guys.
你花費我
You cost me...
太多  太多  喬依
a hell of a lot, Joey, a hell of a lot.
看起來你已經解決了所有的問題
Looks like you're doing all right over here.
是啊  對啊  對啊
Yeah, I am, I am.
我現在還是麻煩不斷
I'm still behind the eightball...
就是因為你
because of you.
我們缺少了某種尊重
There's a certain lack of respect...
缺少了某種信任
a certain lack of trust.
那些在波士頓的人還等著我去呢
The boys in Boston are just waiting for me to go down.
你一直不斷的給我製造麻煩  喬依
You always were a problem for me, Joey.
當媽媽把你從醫院接回來的時候
When Mom brought you home from the hospital...
我就想把你掐死在搖籃裡
I tried to strangle you in your crib.
我想所有的孩子都要那麼多
I guess all kids try to do that.
她發現了我
She caught me...
我就沒好日子過了
whacked the daylights out of me.
我聽說過這個事情
I've heard that story.
是嗎  你怎麼想?
Well, what do you think?
晚點總比不殺好?
Better late than never?
瑞奇
Richie...
我到這裡來只是來尋求和平
I'm here to make peace.
告訴我怎麼做才好
Tell me what I got to do to make things right.
我猜  你可以做一些事情
You could do something, I guess.
你死了就可以了  喬依
You could die, Joey.
你怎麼可以失手?
How do you fuck that up?
你準備幹什麼?  給他人工呼吸嗎?
What are you going to do, give him mouth-to-mouth?
你看到我兄弟了嗎?
Did you see my brother?
媽的 不要管這個
Fuckin' leave this...
我們一起去殺掉那個混蛋
and let's just kill that little fuck!
上帝啊  喬依
Jesus, Joey.
上帝啊 瑞奇
Jesus, Richie.